MANAN AGGARWAL

CONTENT WRITER

Engaging and creative writer with 3+ years of experience, skilled in SEO content writing, short-form content, long-form content, marketing and developing a unique brand voice. Increased clients' online traffic and user engagement by 60% over 11 month, resulting in 30% more lead generation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior SEO Content Writer | Gush

Feb 2024 - Present

· Working with US clients in strategising and providing optimized articles for various verticals and channels.

<u>Freelance Content Writer | Pepper Content</u>

Feb 2023 - Present

• Completed research-intensive SEO articles for clients like Adani Ent., PW, Park+, etc.

Content Writer | Simpl

Mar 2023 - Jul 2023

 Worked on new B2C and D2C product launch and handling all the marketing and finance content.

Copywriter & Lead SEO Content Writer | Variance Marketing Oct 2021 - Aug 2022

- Consistently wrote 9+ Facebook Ads per week to generate fresh leads and increased revenue by 30%.
- Wrote well-researched 500+ SEO articles monthly for various niches to rank the website in the top 30% of searches.

Blog Writer | Happenings LPU

Jun 2021 - Jul 2023

 Structured content creation for promotional events which increased the audience engagement by 40% through blogs.

SKILLS

- SEO Writing
- Copywriting
- Keyword Analysis
- Report Writing (RFP, DDQ, RFI, RFQ)
- Research and Drafting

- Persuasion
- Collaboration
- Communication Skills
- Adaptability
- Efficiency

EDUCATION

Computer Science Engineering | Lovely Professional University 2020-2024

CGPA: 8.60

Minor in Economics

Intermediate | Lord Mahavira Academy

2019-2020

Percentage: 94.2%

AWARDS AND CERTIFICATIONS

- Secured top 100 rank in India in English International Olympiad. (2019)
- Hosted and anchored university-level events.
- Won university level debate competition, "Demospeak 2021".
- Certified by NASBA and PMI in ESG Reporting and Investment Analysis

+917599122100

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/manan-agg



Punjab, India

